Welcome back guys!
Welcome back to a new week and welcome back to a new vlog.
Today feels like Monday because yesterday was a holiday in France and so I was
off.
Today's Tuesday and I'm going back to work.
We had a really nice long weekend.
We went to an area I had never been before in the countryside called Boussoulon.
It was so beautiful.
We went there with friends.
We did barbecues, canoe cake, and fishing and things like that.
And it's now back to work.
I am going to the office.
We have two very big priorities today.
It is content planning day.
We have many contents that we shot and we need to plan them throughout the
year on the Twin Flame account and newsletters and things like that.
and we are doing a big big um new collection development
appointment together we've gathered all of our ideas i've gathered everything that i've seen lately
that's sparked ideas and we're just going to figure out what we'll be doing what
prototype we should be launching and things like that.
I bought myself a little snack, pomegranate, pineapple, and I was craving coconut water.
I also have a little bit of a headache and when I have coconut water
it kind of helps.
Coconut water for the sister.
It's not from the coconut as you're used to.
Yeah, but I'll take it.
You'll take it.
We are matching on necklaces.
You have the gold version.
I didn't even see i think i need to collect other colors you know what
i love i love the black one and i love the red one sisters i'm
wearing the silver version and i really love this piece like it's really fun because
you can make it short make it long it's like a very versatile little type
piece of jewelry i don't really wear necklaces in the winter but in the summer
it really brings something to...
I was telling Lisa, I've been using the bronzer by Merit and I really love
it.
I love the highlighter.
The highlighter is insane.
And I've been using the Merit bronzer with the brush from Makeup by Mario.
And it's very natural.
It's very beautiful.
First slide is ideas for simple jersey tops like the Bella, like the Georgia and
everything.
So that was the idea we already had.
I love that.
We love that.
And then this is another one that I really love because I think it's very
dress up dress down.
I love that you have the same detail as the Bella top like the straight
little part.
Yeah, such a cute piece to have.
What?
Not because we never wear a film.
Good morning everyone.
I am here in the cab with Miss Lisa.
We're very much, it's our preppy vibe.
We're both wearing white and cream because we are going to the French
tennis tournament called Roland-Garros.
It's our first time for both of us.
We're invited by the lingerie brand called Etam.
You guys always love my black satin robe that I wear often in my vlogs.
It is from that brand, from Etam, because I get so many messages to know
where that robe is from.
We've arrived.
He felt we were very much lost.
And it's like this new man.
He's like, you have to go that road and that road.
So you go to door 49.
The girls are growing.
So one thing, my dad is a huge fan of tennis.
He's having major, major FOMO.
Like right now he is asking us every minute if we have arrived and if
we can send him videos.
I wish we could have invited him.
Yes, he would have loved it.
Then once we have a little spot, I'm going to show you Lisa's look.
What's her take on a tennis tournament?
And then I'll show you my look.
What's my take on the tennis tournament?
What about this bag?
Yeah, that I bought, you know, remember where did I buy?
Portugal.
Portugal, Lisbon last year.
It's bringing back memories.
That's right, you know, instead of buying a...
So exciting!
Lisa's look of the day, little white skirt, white linen shirt, sunnies.
Cheese.
Look at that.
You guys, I've been shooting Lisa on this little corner right here and of course
everyone can see you everyone's now shooting this and i was kind of embarrassed when
she said go and shoot those like off in front of everyone i said it's
the perfect angle you have a thing in the back everybody's doing their thing everyone's
everyone we just had lunch and we're going back to watch a new game and
now we're gonna watch elena zvitolina and caitlyn kevil spain against ukraine let's go
I'm going to go to the next one.
Okay,
end of the Roland Garros for me.
Lisa stayed there for the last game with Djokovic and Valentin Royer.
I unfortunately had to leave early while it was planned.
I have a job, a modeling job at 4.30pm.
It is 3.50pm.
I have 40 minutes to get there which should be fine.
But it's a walk to the metro.
It's like 18 minutes walk with Google.
So I don't know if you guys are like me but when Google tells me
18 minutes walk, it's 10 in my mind because i'm fast walker but it's extremely
warm today and i don't want to arrive there like looking disheveled and sweaty so
i'm trying to pace myself i'm so sad i'm missing the last game i would
have loved to watch it i've never seen a game um with djokovic so you
know he's a legend so i would have loved to see the game if i
have a documentary to recommend well too actually i have one called
point break uh really good they follow new talents um
on netflix in the you know so it's really a documentary style a little bit
like drive to survive i think it's the same yeah it's the same people so
it's kind of fun and then the other one is untold with a specific
player i think it was fisher very very good and i think
very very
soon is coming out a documentary about nadal on netflix so i'm definitely watching that
i realize I realized recently how many like
sports documentary I watch.
Like I watch all of them.
I love them all.
I love, I just love the world of sports in general.
Good evening.
It's 8pm and finally back home.
Djokovic ended up winning the game.
It lasted super long, Lisa said.
I think they had finished at like 7pm and they started at 4.
so that was a really long game.
I'm preparing dinner and I'm so thirsty and I've been drinking water water but it
feels like it's not working.
It's not making me less thirsty.
So I'm making my boyfriend and I a little mocktail.
So I've added some crushed ice.
It's not really a mocktail.
the easiest thing in the world crushed ice in a nice wine glass i buy
instead of buying lemons sometimes i bite this just because it's easier to just add
to your water any time of the day it's organic lemon juice it's only lemon
juice there's nothing else like no sugar no nothing
Mocktails done.
To go with the mocktails, I'm making a little apiajo because I'm making potatoes for
the bean dish tonight and it's going to take a little bit of time starving.
So, so let's prepare the potatoes first, get them into the oven, then do the
apiajo together.
so
A
little
apéro, carrots, hummus and smoked scamorza.
Delicious.
Good evening guys.
Another taxi introduction.
Lisa and I have had so many events this week.
And we're going to another one together.
Tonight is one that we've been waiting for a really long time.
Because we were invited like a month ago.
A month ago, yeah.
And it's actually a Summer Fridays event.
So we're so excited.
Because we've been loving the brand since it started.
The Jet Lag Mask is one of my favorite skincare products.
I don't remind myself to buy it enough.
I used to always repurchase it.
I have it in a mini size.
and it's very convenient.
I love this thing like it's really really good but I always forget to buy
it and they don't always have it here in France.
Yeah they keep some on Fridays.
Oh my god it's huge!
The event is at a restaurant we've been twice together.
It's called the Grand Café.
It's inside the twice at night and at lunch um it's inside the uh company
he says look of the night i think you guys recognize it i had it
in london and then she also purchased it because it's so cute and it's on
sale at the moment up
We're
having a great week.
Lisa sat there at that table.
We're eating all the desserts.
We had already peach and creams.
Now we're having the Franboisier.
She's sitting there and I am sitting here on the other side.
As if we don't know each other.
We're chit-chatting.
We're debriefing from there.
Good morning guys.
You guys are not ready for what I'm about to say about where I am
at the moment but okay last night was a blast we had so much fun
at the summer friday's party uh we met amelia liana which has a youtube channel
that we adore with lisa and she was the sweetest then i went to a
birthday party and i went to bed at 2 30 a.m and woke up at
6.
so we could be here today took a train to poitiers which is the city
um down south and we are at an event called
500 Ferrari against cancer?
Yeah.
Okay.
So yeah, 500 Ferraris against cancer.
It's a charity event that's organized.
And so people from all over the world come into their Ferraris.
There's some racing, there's things like that.
And they, of course, raise money to research against cancer.
It is only 11 a.m.
and it's like a thousand degrees.
I don't know how I'm gonna survive this day.
I realized I didn't take any like bobby pins or something to put my hair
up.
I think I am gonna be going into a sports car to get driven around
like really fast which I am absolutely terrified about because I get very much carsick.
So here we are!
What
are we wearing at a
car event?
I'm wearing this bodysuit, a pair of kind of high-waisted jeans, my Gucci boots, my
courage bag and a hairpin and my valley eyewear and I just
got out of the driver's brief not driving but I'm gonna get driven into a
car on the circuit which I am absolutely terrified
first because I just had a huge hot dog and fries and I feel like
you know and that's it so The deal is, basically people come with their
cars and they offer for a certain amount of money to go around with the
car.
This money is then given to research
for all types of research for cancer.
That's the whole deal of this weekend, which I think is pretty cool because it's
passionate people.
People get to go into cars they've always dreamed to try and it's helping to
fight cancer.
That is amazing.
I'm going to die.
Die?
It's happening guys.
It's happening.
I'm terrified.
Oh my god.
Tada!
Okay, I'm ready.
All the cars have been lining up guys.
guys.
My boyfriend's driving, so I trust him.
He's a very, very good driver, but you know that feeling, it's not for me.
It's not for me.
Thank
you.
🎵 My legs are shaking guys, I just got out of it.
I don't know if I want to vomit or cry.
You guys, we're on our way back to Paris and we are watching a Rodin-Garros
game.
Two days ago, Moise Courmet won a game
and he's the youngest player to have won a game in a Grand Slam since
1991.
He's French and we're like rooting for him like crazy and he has now won
his first set so we're like this.
You
guys, we got home, the tennis game is still not done and we also have
the football game.
Since we can't choose, we've been just watching both of them at the same time.
Good evening guys.
is a very sporty evening.
Tennis match, unfortunately, Maurice Cormier lost, so Roland-Garros is over for him.
On the football side, the Paris Saint-Germain Club won.
I don't know if you guys can hear, it is mayhem in the streets of
Paris, it's insane.
Like, we personally had planned to not go out tonight because we knew that it
would be crazy to just even be walking in the streets.
So we are tucked into our little apartment while everyone is celebrating in the streets.
And now we are watching the Netflix documentary about Rafael
Nadal, and it's excellent.
Guys, they're so good at doing documentaries, like sports documentaries on Netflix.
And this one, once again, delivers.
And also because his story is so rich, there's so much to talk about and
unpack and tell and the little untold stories and all that.
It's fascinating.
I highly recommend.
After spending these two days in a very extreme heat, no shade, a lot of
dust, my skin is in a desperate need of a little reset.
I just showered, cold shower, and I'm first gonna remove my makeup with the 10
hectares Bon Fertile.
I love this when I wanna do like a thorough cleanse, deep cleanse, this really
removes my makeup within one wash, I would say.
And I just love to massage this in for a while.
I found this.
A bundle for skincare.
It's perfect.
I'm of course going to double cleanse.
I'm going to use the Zectaf cleanser.
I was literally falling asleep.
and I was like, no, I didn't do all this to not finish the skincare
routine.
So I'm now going to do a mask.
I want this to be quick.
So I'm going to do the Goop Beauty Microderm Instant Glow Exfoliator.
I love this to just reset my skin, give it a nice exfoliation,
but you just need to leave this for three minutes.
So it's perfect when you don't want to spend too much time doing your
skincare, but it still gives that feeling of really
well exfoliated, cleansed skin.
This mask is a combination of two types of exfoliation.
It does a manual exfoliation, so it has these little seeds, I would say, and
also a chemical exfoliation.
So it's a pretty complete mask.
You just let it sit for three minutes to let the chemicals do their thing.
I've done this so many times, and honestly, like, little goes a long way.
so that's been in my vanity since september almost a year crazy and i'm seeing
this because it is a pricey product but i don't mind splurging in masks because
you don't do them that often so it lasts long put away a little bit
my things from my um from my little night troop
i also got a little sample of this Tata Harper Super Kind
Radiance Mask.
It's so good.
It just wakes your skin up, makes it feel very fresh.
Really love this.
And this is really nice.
Also, funnily enough, I've done it at night when I need a little boost, but
I've also done it in the morning when I just want my face to feel
alive, I guess, before like a makeup or an important day.
So really nice.
And also this one, the little goes a long way.
See, I've already done it a few times and there's still a lot left.
Next, I'm going to do the Summer Serum by Desicta.
You guys are going to say that I'm only using the brand, but I don't
know.
I was gravitating towards this today.
Here's what it is.
Nice layer of serum.
We've been tearing up the whole weekend.
We've been tearing up while watching the documentary, especially at the beginning when he announces
the fact that he was going to stop his professional tennis career.
and yesterday seeing also the people so excited to drive in cars that they dream
of and things like that and they were so cute we kept like getting so
emotional and it's also for a cause that's like dear to my heart so dear
to his heart and so we were like super emotional the whole day yesterday and
then today we watched this we're like tearing up in bed and i'm like what's
going on now the PD PDR and 100 cream I have nothing
to say about this one it's not bad but it's not exceptional so it's not
a product I will repurchase I think I don't know but it's
a nice thick cream
that penetrates well
But I think I've tried others from Korean cosmetic brands that just felt way
more effective.
Last step, and this one I love.
I'm going to do the Medi-Cube Wrapping Collagen Night Mask.
I love this.
This is one of my favorite masks.
I do a really thick layer.
You really have to do this like 15 minutes before you fall asleep just to
have the time to dry.
And then tomorrow morning you just peel it off.
It's really not uncomfortable to sleep in, which is not the case of the Biodance
mask, which I love but can be a little bit more annoying to sleep with
so
that's why i really really love this one a little bit of the help preserve
peptide lip treatment in there i'm ready for bed good afternoon
guys it's Monday today.
I am all ready to go to my modeling agency for a little Polaroid shoot.
That's why I'm you know going makeup free and all of that.
I'm at home.
When I was in Bali I received a few gifts from brands and I thought
I'd just look into it and show a little bit to you guys what I've
received because I think you guys might like a few of the things that I
got.
And sometimes it's just nice to do a little shopping spree together, a little lèche
vitrine as we say, window shopping or something like that.
So here we are.
The first thing I wanted to show you guys is actually something that we got
in our Etam Goodie Bag at the Roland Garros event.
It's this sunscreen.
It's sunscreen season, right?
So I know you guys are looking for good recommendations.
This is from SVR.
It's a 50 plus.
And what's really interesting is that it's a moisturizing sun water.
So I thought it'd be a little bit oily, see, because you have kind of
that oily effect.
But when you spray it on the skin, it leaves a really nice shine, but
it feels like water.
It doesn't feel heavy and it sinks into the skin straight away, which is something
I love.
I feel that sometimes when you're hot and it can be humid and things like
that, you don't want things sitting on your skin and that feel greasy and all
that and also this is a sunscreen that is safe for corals so that's a
great point i've received the most gorgeous package by ysl beauty it's like you know
these little books that you have in your hotel room that has all the information
of your hotel it even had this like please do not disturb sign so cute
so thoughtful and I just love to have this like in my um how to
say library I think I'm gonna bring it to the office I think it's very
cool for a little office inside we have new lip products from the YSL love
nude blur the line in term of lip liner I think I'd try a little
bit more of this than the others So this is definitely the pink of the
box.
So pretty.
Sculpting lip liner one.
Then this is 102.
Yeah, that's way more my color.
See, a little bit more brownish.
Browner shade 109.
Yeah, see way more dark.
But then we have three lipsticks.
This is number one.
Very pretty color.
super pigmented a kind of satin finish it's not matte it's not shiny it's satin
this one's a little darker red okay here you have it this is the number
two oh this is more my vibe see it's a little bit more yeah brownish
here we go i love to try new makeup because it makes me try new
things and kind of
Get out of my comfort zone, you know?
Gonna dab like that.
Oh, that's a pretty lip.
Very pretty.
It brought life to me, right?
This, I mean, the packaging of this.
It's a book and the perfume is inside.
How beautiful is this?
It's so romantic.
I love it.
The perfume is from Maison Margiela.
It's called Fite of Folie.
It's a very unisex scent.
It's super powerful, but super fresh.
So I feel like it's pretty perfect for summer.
The bottle is so pretty.
I mean, this is insanely gorgeous.
It's a beautiful scent.
It's funny, if I were in the store, I don't know if I would purchase
this for myself.
But now that I have it, I'm like, should I explore this type of scent
for myself?
You see what I mean?
Next up, we have a hair care brand called Care.
Really beautiful.
I have here the shampoo, the serum, leave-in kind of conditioner.
And this is more of a styling cream.
I also have the hair mask.
I will let you know.
These are things I really need to try before I can have any type of
opinion.
Then we have a skincare brand I've heard of many, many times.
It's called Glory.
It's vegan.
It's made in Korea.
Here we have the jelly cream.
This is the
jelly face wash.
I also have the facial exfoliant toner.
Look at that.
It looks like a jello.
see it literally is jello how do you okay
that is such a weird consistency that's very fun yeah no scent here either
okay very refreshing definitely need to try this out the piece the piece
the bag piece it's from this brand called verified new york i don't know if
you guys have seen this around they have many many gorgeous styles gorgeous um
leathers and things like that and the price point honestly is impeccable for the quality
of uh the pieces but also I think they really have some really
cool styles.
This is one of their best-selling pieces.
It's a clutch, a black leather clutch.
I got it with the silver hardware just because I didn't have anything black and
silver and I felt like it was really missing in my closet.
Something that just can really go with many many different looks especially at night it's
a roomy clutch so see you can really put a lot of things in here
so that's very practical it also comes with two types of handles but this handles
like this you have this short version that i guess you come and clip here
but i don't know how yet i literally had to go on youtube to see
a tutorial of how to put little straps in so basically you have here the
clips and you unclip it like that so you secure like that you unclip it
and then you just
slide it in like so i love it as a clutch but with the little
handles it's perfect oh that is the perfect like clutch but still with a handle
nighttime bag.
Oh my gosh.
And they have it in brown.
It's gorgeous.
They have it in a snake skin.
It's beautiful.
This is so pretty.
You have longer shoulder straps, so that's perfect for more of a daily look.
Oh, I love this.
This is so pretty.
Oh, this is such a perfect bag and it's very chic.
It's like little short handles.
And this is the end of this vlog, my friends.
I hope you enjoyed this very eventful week it was a week of events thank
you so much for watching i hope you guys enjoyed coming with me to all
these little events i had fun sharing them with you guys i wish you all
an amazing week i wish you all a beautiful day or a beautiful night wherever
you are and i'll catch you guys in my next video bye guys
you